<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Kyle David Rudy\n yduR divaD elyK]]></title><description><![CDATA[Yea, you know wonk uoy ,aeY]]></description><link>https://kdrudy.github.io</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 20:18:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kdrudy.github.io/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Slack Hand Raising Bot]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>So in the run up to class I&#8217;ve been working on a Slack bot that will allow students to anonymously ask questions.  It&#8217;s been intersesting to dive into the Slack API.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I&#8217;m using <a href="https://github.com/ramswaroop/jbot">JBot</a> a Spring based Java framework for building Slack bots.  It can help you write slash commands, straight-forward bots, and tie into incoming and outgoing webhooks.  I startd writing a slash command but realized those don&#8217;t end up being anonymous since anyone can see the slash command you entered so that&#8217;s when I moved on to writing a bot.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The idea behind the bot is that you direct message it a question and it will ask your question in the Slack channel for your class anonymously.  We don&#8217;t want any student to be afraid to ask questions.  The trick with the bot ended up being that your direct messages only contain the senders user ID, so I had to convert that into a user name in order to properly route it.  User IDs in Slack are not easy to find unless you are working directly with the API, so for ease of use I&#8217;m routing based on user name.  When we match the user name to a class, I can then send a question to the right channel.  I had to access Slack&#8217;s Web API and get user info from that in JSON form, there was no good way to get that data from inside <a href="https://github.com/ramswaroop/jbot">JBot</a>, though it looks like the guy who made it plans to add Web API functionality in the future.  For now I&#8217;m managing it myself and it worked like a charm.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I&#8217;m using Spring&#8217;s <code>application.properties</code> file to maintain the class channel, instructor and list of students.  That should make it relatively easy for non-Java users to go in and update if I&#8217;m ever not available to make an update.</p>
</div>]]></description><link>https://kdrudy.github.io/2016/10/10/Slack-Hand-Raising-Bot.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://kdrudy.github.io/2016/10/10/Slack-Hand-Raising-Bot.html</guid><category><![CDATA[slack]]></category><category><![CDATA[ jbot]]></category><category><![CDATA[ the iron yard]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Kyle David Rudy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Old License Terms]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>This is my favorite part of the old Sun Java license, hard to track down:</p>
</div>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>4.  High Risk Activities.  Notwithstanding Section 2, with respect to
high risk activities, the following language shall apply: the Software
is not designed or intended for use in on-line control of aircraft,
air traffic, aircraft navigation or aircraft communications; or in the
design, construction, operation or maintenance of any nuclear
facility. Sun disclaims any express or implied warranty of fitness for
such uses.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>]]></description><link>https://kdrudy.github.io/2016/08/08/Old-License-Terms.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://kdrudy.github.io/2016/08/08/Old-License-Terms.html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Kyle David Rudy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blog Post]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>What a testing post, wow hey how is it going, pretty good huh, crazy right, well see ya!</p>
</div>]]></description><link>https://kdrudy.github.io/2016/08/04/Blog-Post.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://kdrudy.github.io/2016/08/04/Blog-Post.html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Kyle David Rudy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>